Finding Aid for Cornelia G. Kennedy papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
To some extent, the history of information and communications technology during the period is also represented in the collection through its examples of different correspondence media in different eras and through materials pertaining to the advent of computer-aided legal research in court libraries and the use of new technologies in federal courtrooms.
Inevitably, Judge Kennedy's long family history in the practice of law coincided with significant milestones in American history and in the development of judicial administration organizations and policy. Kennedy's father had graduated from law school and begun his legal career with World War I on the horizon. Kennedy graduated from law school as the national economy was transforming itself after World War II, and as the federal court system was beginning a new era in judicial practice and in judicial review of administration.
Description of Series Content
This collection is divided into ten series: Personal and Biographical; Correspondence; Speeches and Writings; Wayne County Circuit Court; U.S. District Court, Eastern District of Michigan; U.S. Court of Appeals, 6th Circuit; Judicial Conference of the United States; Federal Judicial Center; American Bar Association; and Other Professional Organizations and Meetings.
Of necessity, some series include materials of multiple formats, located together primarily with regard to conceptual content rather than format and some types of materials are found in multiple series. For example, correspondence can be found not only in the Correspondence series but also within court-related series to the extent that it relates to matters addressed there.
Throughout the collection, Judge Kennedy's own phrasing is used whenever possible to describe file folder contents. Some examples of her original file folders of administrative papers and office files also contain handwritten notes and have been retained in the collection to provide additional information to the researcher. These original folder labels and notations also help to illustrate the use of different terminology in different time frames.
Subjects:
Federal Judicial Center.; Judicial Conference of the United States.; Judicial Conference of the United States. Committee to Review Circuit Council Conduct and Disability Orders.; Judicial ethics--United States.; Kennedy, Cornelia G. (Cornelia Groefsema), 1923-2014.; Michigan. Circuit Court (Wayne County); United States. Court of Appeals (6th Circuit); United States. District Court (Michigan: Eastern District); University of Michigan. Law School--Alumni and alumnae.; Women judges--Michigan--Detroit.; Women judges--United States.
Genre Terms:
Interviews (Sound recordings); Photographs.
- Personal and Biographical 1932-2012
  The Personal and Biographical series (2.5 linear feet, including audio-visual materials, 4.78 GB online, and 1 oversize folder, 1932-2012), is divided into four subseries: Collected Personal Material; University of Michigan Law School; News Media; and Audio-Visual Material. Most of the folders in this series, including some containing correspondence, were placed into this category by Judge Kennedy.
  - Collected Personal Material
    The subseries contains Judge Kennedy's curriculum vitae and biographical sketches, appointment books and calendars, personal correspondence, invitations to interview and speaking engagements, and other material of biographical and personal nature.
    - Certificate of Admission to Practice in U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia 1949 (Folder 1)
    - National College of State Trial Judges, University of Nevada, Chart of Participant Photos 1968 (Folder 1)
    - 'Odds and Ends' of Memorabilia circa 1932-1967 (Box 1)
    - Family Archive 1944-1975, 1985, 2003 (Box 1)
    - 'Old Activities,' 1963-1966 (Box 1)
    - Biographical Information 1968-1999, 8 folders (Box 1)
    - Michigan Association of the Professions Monitor, "The First Decade," Anniversary and Roster Issue, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Oath of Office Ceremony, U.S. District Court Judge 1970 (Box 1)
    - Women's Economic Club, Women Who Work Award 1971 (Box 1)
    - Appointment Books and Calendars
      - 1974 (Box 1)
      - 1979-1987, 3 folders (Box 1)
      - 1993 (Box 1)
    - Commission on the Bicentennial of the U.S. Constitution 1985, 1997 (Box 1)
    - WQED-TV (Pittsburgh, PA), Interview in Cincinnati, Ohio 1987-1990 (Box 1)
    - Nomination, Edward J. Devitt Distinguished Service to Justice Award 1998-1999 (Box 1)
    - Michigan Women's Hall of Fame, Life Achievement Award 1999-2000 (Box 1)
    - Portrait Dedication Correspondence 2002 (Box 1)
    - Detroit Bar Association, Frank Murphy Award 2011 (Box 1)
    - Historical Society for the U.S. District Court, Eastern District of Michigan, Article on the "...Nomination and Appointment Process of Women to the Bench...," 2012
  - University of Michigan Law School
    The subseries includes invitations and programs of alumni reunions and events.
    - Institute of Continuing Legal Education, 20th Annual Advocacy Institute, Hutchins Hall, Ann Arbor, Michigan 1969 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Visitors
      - Correspondence 1970-1977 (Box 1)
      - Meeting Agenda, Member List, and Reports 1993 (Box 1)
    - Alumnae Events
      - Women Law Students Association Speech 1978 (Box 1)
      - Midwest Regional Conference for Women in Law 1979 (Box 1)
      - Women's Success 1997-1998 (Box 1)
    - Class Reunions
      - Reunion Directory, Class of 1945, 1946 and 1947, two Personal Photographs outside Law School 1961 (Box 1)
      - Alumni Reunion and Law Forum 1982 (Box 1)
      - 40th Reunion of the Class of 1947
        - Program Planning Correspondence 1987 (Box 2)
        - Class Roster 1987 (Box 2)
      - 45th Reunion, 1946 and 1947, Class Notes 1992 (Box 2)
      - 50th Reunion 1997 (Box 2)
  - News Media
    The subseries, News Media, includes newspaper clippings and articles about Judge Kennedy.
    - Miscellaneous 1960s
      - Newspaper Clippings 1960-1967 (Box 2)
      - Judicial Campaign 1965-1966 (Box 2)
      - General 1968 (Box 2)
      - Long-running Wayne County Circuit Court Case 1969 (Box 2)
    - Newsclips, Re: Supreme Court [of the United States] 1971 (Box 2)
    - U.S. Judicial Conference (1st woman district judge) 1978 (Box 2)
    - Senate Confirmation Process (for U.S. Circuit Court)
      - Detroit News Announces "Another First," 1979 (Box 2)
      - Political Labels and Editorial Opinions 1979 (Box 2)
      - Senate Confirmation Announced 1979 (Box 2)
      - Oath of Office, Federal Appellate Court, 6th Circuit 1979 (Box 2)
    - Federal Court Candidacy (Additional) 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Later Supreme Court Possibilities
      - Part 1 of 4 1975 (Box 2)
      - Part 2 of 4 1975-1977 (Box 2)
      - Part 3 of 4 1978 (Box 2)
      - Part 4 of 4 1992, 1998 (Box 2)
    - The Detroit News Magazine, 1978 (Box 2)
    - National Enquirer, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Article on Runaways (August pages 76-83) New Woman Magazine, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Women 1977 (Box 2)
    - Chief Judge, Federal District Court 1977-1978 (Box 2)
    - Newsclips, Personal 1970-1972 (Box 2)
    - General
      - 1981-1985 (Box 2)
      - 1995-2007, 4 folders (Box 2)
  - Audio-Visual Materials
    The subseries, Audio-Visual Materials, includes Judge Kennedy's portraits as well as group portraits with other judges; recorded audio and video interviews, and other related recorded segments.
    - Photographs and Slides
      - 1950s, 1960s, 1956-1970 (Box 2)
      - Proofs circa 1965 (Box 2)
      - Large, Portrait-style with backboard, undated circa 2002 (Box 3)
      - Matted Photographs and Photographic Slides undated
        - circa 1947 1970 (Box 3)
        - circa 1980 (Box 3)
      - Wayne County Circuit Court circa 1967, 2 envelopes (Box 3)
      - 1960s circa 1968 (Box 3)
      - With Senator Robert Griffin 1970 (Box 3)
      - As Chief Judge, Federal District Court 1979 (Box 3)
      - Smaller Photographs and Negatives, some undated
        - 1979, 1985, 1993 (Box 3)
        - Miscellaneous 1974, circa 2005-2006 (Box 3)
    - Symposium on Women in the American Judiciary, "Conversations from Wingspread," the Johnson Foundation, Racine, Wisconsin 1982, audiocassette tape (Box 3)
    - Women Trailblazers in the Law Project Oral History Interview
      (Conducted by Allyson A. Miller)
      - Biographical Information and Curricula Vitae for Justice Kennedy and Allyson Miller 2012, .ZIP file)
        [Download restricted to BHL Reading Room]
      - Photographs of Justice Kennedy with Colleagues and Family circa 1950-2008, .ZIP file
      - Sound Recordings and Transcripts 2012, .WAV, .DOC, .PDF, and .ZIP files
    - Videotaped Topics
      - "Judicial Activities and Ethics," Speaker: the Honorable Cornelia G. Kennedy; Seminar for Newly Appointed U.S. District Judges, Washington, D.C. June 21, 1979 (Box 3)
        (videocassette tape, color)
      - "Appellate Advocacy: A Viewpoint from an Appellate Judge," Hon. Cornelia Kennedy circa 1980, videocassette tape (Box 3)
        (see American Bar Association series)
      - "Visions of the Constitution," WQED, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania 1987, audiocassette tape, 1 hour 8 minutes
        (videocassette tape set)
        - #101, Search for Equality (57:53) (Box 3)
        - #102, The Judges (57:23) (Box 3)
        - #103, Crime and the Bill of Rights (57:36) (Box 3)
      - "America Celebrates the Bicentennial of the United States Constitution," Commission on the Bicentennial of the U. S. Constitution circa 1989 (Box 3)
        (videocassette tape)
      - "Commemoration of the Bicentennial of the U. S. Constitution," The Ad Council circa 1989 (Box 3)
- Correspondence 1967-2012
  The Correspondence series (2.75 linear feet, 1967-2012), contains judicial correspondence of a more general nature, some categorized as personal, and correspondence from the public. Some of the correspondence included here reflects subject areas found in other series of this collection, as well as in-depth discussion among judges. For example, judicial correspondence includes articles (1996-1999) on different sentencing norms for possession of different illegal drugs, notably crack versus cocaine sentences.
  - Personal
    - 1967-1979, 14 folders (Box 3)
    - 1980-2012, 5 folders (Box 4)
    - Law Students 1971-1977 (Box 4)
    - Attorneys 1971-1977, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Legislators 1971-1978 (Box 4)
    - Supreme Court Eligibility and Recommendations 1971, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Women's Economic Club 1978 (Box 4)
    - Federal Judicial Center 1971-1979 (Box 4)
    - Administrative Office of the U.S. Courts
      - 1973, 1976-1977, 1993 (Box 4)
      - Electronic Communication Initiatives 1998-2000 (Box 4)
      - Judicial Salaries 1999 (Box 4)
    - Judges
      - 6th Circuit 1972-1980 (Box 4)
      - Smith, Talbot 1974-1979 (Box 4)
      - Eastern District of Michigan 1970-1978 (Box 4)
      - Other 1971-1980, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Administrative Office of the U.S. Courts 1993-1998, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - U.S. District Court, Eastern District of Michigan
    - Administrative
      - History and Future 1993-1995 (Box 4)
      - Federal Judicial Center 1977-1980 (Box 4)
      - Requests for Publication of Opinions 1974-1975 (Box 4)
    - Communication between Judges
      - Impressions of John Feikens for his Portrait Ceremony 2006 (Box 4)
      - 1976-1979, 12 folders (Box 4)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1995-2000 (Box 5)
    - Judicial
      - 1994-2011, 4 folders (Box 5)
      - "Other related," 1982-2005 (Box 5)
    - Senior Status 1999-2011 (Box 5)
  - General
    - 1972-1979, 11 folders (Box 5)
    - 1994-1997 (Box 5)
  - Invitations, Speaking Engagements, Interviews
    - 1970-1980, 11 folders (Box 5)
    - 1982 (Box 5)
    - 1995-2000 (Box 5)
  - Unsolicited
    - Freedom of Information Act Request 1995 (Box 6)
    - Dismissed Complaint of Judicial Misconduct 1990-1998 (Box 6)
    - Goodman, Jim 1983-1994 (Box 6)
    - 1984-1996, 3 folders (Box 6)
- Speeches and Writings 1967-2006
  Speeches and Writings (1 linear foot, 1967-2006), is a series that highlights some, but certainly not all, of Judge Kennedy's speeches at various meetings and events, as well as some of her writings. The series is divided into two subseries: Transcripts and Drafts; and Resource Material for Speeches.
  - Transcripts and Drafts
    The subseries contains transcripts and drafts of speeches, occasionally accompanied by event programs and related correspondence.
    - Introducing and/or Honoring other Judges
      - John Feikens 1986, 2006 (Box 6)
      - Ralph B. Guy, Jr. 1998 (Box 6)
      - Damon J. Keith 1990 (Box 6)
      - Investiture of James L. Ryan 1986 (Box 6)
    - Federal Bar Association, Eastern District of Michigan Chapter, Edward H. Rakow Awards 1999 (Box 6)
    - Appellate Advocacy
      - Speech at the U.S. Attorney General's Advocacy Institute, Washington, D.C. 1992 (Box 6)
      - Article for Michigan Bar Journal, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
      - Speech at 6th Circuit Practice Institute 1995 (Box 6)
    - Honoring Mary Beck, 1st Woman (1950) Detroit City Council Member circa 1994 (Box 6)
    - Judicial Fellows Program 1993 (Box 6)
    - New Lawyers Speech circa 1988 (Box 6)
    - Celebrating our Constitution Speech 1986-1987 (Box 6)
    - Speeches as an Appellate Court Judge 1980-1982 (Box 6)
    - Immigration and Naturalization 1980 (Box 6)
    - Early Career Speeches as a Judge 1969-1979 (Box 6)
    - Undated Early Career Speeches as a Judge circa 1967-1978 (Box 6)
  - Resource Material for Speeches
    The subseries contains topical material she accumulated in researching and preparing for speeches, as well as materials related to a published journal article she authored on appellate advocacy.
    - Appellate Advocacy 1951-1992 (Box 6)
    - Women in Law 1973-1999 (Box 6)
    - Judicial Ethics 1966, 1977-1979 (Box 7)
    - National Court of Appeals 1983-1985 (Box 7)
    - General (including role of the jury, tributes to the federal judicial system) 1969-1990 (Box 7)
- Wayne County Circuit Court (3rd Judicial Circuit of Michigan) 1967-1974
  The Wayne County Circuit Court (3rd Judicial Circuit of Michigan) series (0.75 linear feet, 1967-1974), contains correspondence, materials from Judge Kennedy's earliest judicial committee work, and examples of her opinions and other casework in her first role as a judge.
  - Correspondence
    - General 1967-1970 (Box 7)
    - Personal 1970-1974 (Box 7)
  - Committees
    - Rules 1967-1970 (Box 7)
    - Salaries (of Judges) 1968-1970 (Box 7)
  - Appealed Cases 1967-1972 (Box 7)
  - Opinions
    - 1967-1970, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Criminal 1967 (Box 7)
    - Motions for New Trial 1967-1968 (Box 7)
    - Summary Judgments 1967-1968 (Box 7)
    - Sent to Fred Battaglia (Court Reporter) for Wayne State Journal Reporter, 1968-1970 (Box 7)
- U.S. District Court, Eastern District of Michigan 1966-1981
  The U.S. District Court, Eastern District of Michigan series (11 linear feet, 1966-1981), is divided into five subseries: Office Administration; Judge's Meeting Minutes, Memos, and Correspondence; Court Appeals Decisions in Cases Heard by Judge Kennedy; Other Judicial Activities; and Court Cases.
  - Office Administration
    The subseries includes materials related to court administration and procedure.
    - Bankruptcy Committee
      - General 1970-1976, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Local Rules 1973-1975 (Box 8)
      - "To November 1, 1976" 1970-1976 (Box 8)
      - "Beginning November 1, 1976" 1976-1978 (Box 8)
      - Quarterly Reports to Administrative Office 1971-1979 (Box 8)
    - Administrative Office of the United States Courts
      - Memorandum on Ethics for Referees 1966 (Box 8)
      - Referee System Recommendations 1972 (Box 8)
      - Rules of Bankruptcy Procedure and Tables of Bankruptcy Statistics 1974-1975 (Box 8)
    - Special Committees
      - Going off the Draw [of new cases] 1973-1976 (Box 8)
      - Docket of Older Cases for New Judges 1976 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous Court Business and Public Correspondence 1975-1980, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Library Inventory List 1972-1976 (Box 8)
    - General Services Administration 1970-1977 (Box 8)
    - Clerk of the Court 1971-1978 (Box 8)
    - Bench Warrants Issued 1971-1978 (Box 8)
  - Judges' Meeting Minutes, Memos, and Correspondence
    The subseries includes material on committee work and judges' meetings, for example, discussions on the emerging role of bankruptcy and magistrate judges.
    - 1968 (Box 8)
    - 1970 (Box 8)
    - 1971, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - 1972, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - 1973, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - 1974, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - 1975, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - 1976, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - 1977, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - 1978 (Box 9)
    - 1979 (Box 9)
  - Court of Appeals Decisions in Cases Heard by Judge Kennedy
    The subseries includes material regarding cases previously heard by Judge Kennedy.
    - Civil 1971-1980, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Criminal 1973-1980, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Other Judicial Activities
    The subseries includes correspondence and programs of judicial conferences attended by Judge Kennedy, material on Wayne State University Judicial Internship Program, multidistrict litigation, and material related to Judge Kennedy's activities on the Sentencing Council.
    - Judicial Internship Program, Wayne State University 1971-1977 (Box 9)
    - Judicial Conferences, 6th Circuit 1975-1979, 5 folders (Box 9)
    - Juries--Juror--Jury 1972-1977 (Box 9)
    - Multidistrict Litigation #343, Upjohn Company 1978-1981 (2 of 3 folders) (Box 9)
    - Multidistrict Litigation #343, Upjohn Company 1978-1981 (3 of 3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Sentencing Council 1963-1977 (Box 10)
  - Court Cases
    The final subseries is the largest and contains folders representing individual civil and criminal court cases.
    - Civil Cases, 140 folders
      - 35580 to 40060 1971-1973, 36 folders (Box 10)
      - 40276 to 40334 74-70023 to 74-72851 1973-1976, 25 folders (Box 11)
      - 74-81692 to 75-71229 1974-1981, 14 folders (Box 12)
      - 75-71233 to 75-71747 1975-1985, 11 folders (Box 13)
      - 76-70135 to 77-71242 1976-1982, 26 folders (Box 14)
      - 77-71229 to 70-70935 1977-1980, 28 folders (Box 15)
    - Criminal cases, 57 folders
      - 42672 to 49329 1971-1974, 19 folders (Box 16)
      - 74-80323 to 77-80645 1973-1986, 23 folders (Box 17)
      - 77-80678 to 78-80361 1977-1979, 15 folders (Box 18)
- U.S. Court of Appeals, 6th Circuit 1970-2012
  The U.S. Court of Appeals, 6th Circuit series (35 linear feet, 1970-2012), is divided into eight subseries: Nomination and Appointment: Confirmation Process, 1977-1979; Administrative Files; Judicial Conferences; Circuit Court Committee Files; Sixth Circuit Judicial Council; Correspondence; Published Opinions; and Court Cases.
  - Nomination and Appointment: Confirmation Process 1977-1979
    The subseries begins with more than two linear feet of material related to Judge Kennedy's nomination and confirmation for the 6th Circuit Court of Appeals. The subseries contains questionnaires, correspondence, drafts and copies of her testimonies and responses in hearings; statements in support and in opposition to her candidacy; summaries of cases and opinions presented in connection with confirmation hearings; and other related material.
    - Correspondence 1977-1980, 10 folders (Box 19)
    - Writ Clerk Affidavits 1979 (Box 19)
    - Oath of Office Ceremony 1979 (Box 19)
    - Questionnaires 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Judge Kennedy's Testimonies and Responses 1979
      - Testimony at Hearings (Box 19)
      - 1st Response, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - 2nd Response (Box 19)
      - Additional Responses (Box 19)
    - Statements
      - In Support 1979, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Opposing 1979, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Review of Court Cases 1979
      - List of Section 1915(d) Cases undated (Box 20)
      - List of 1977 Social Security Cases, undated (Box 20)
      - List of Level 2-79 Cases undated (Box 20)
      - Affirmations and Reversals 1979 (Box 20)
      - Civil Rights 1973-1974 (Box 20)
      - Police 1970-1978 (Box 20)
      - Prison 1971-1979, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Probation 1977-1978 (Box 20)
      - Race 1973-1978 (Box 20)
      - U.S. v. Hayward Brown 1974 (Box 20)
      - U.S. v. School District of Ferndale 1975-1978 (Box 20)
      - U.S. v. Walter Nugent 1979 (Box 20)
      - Cases sent to Senator Howard M. Metzenbaum 1979
        - Canfield West-Wayne Preservation Association, Inc. v. City of Detroit, Michigan 1979 (Box 20)
        - Civil rights or Constitutional Cases 1971-1978 (Box 20)
        - Consent Judgments 1975-1978 (Box 20)
        - Giles v. Milliken 1976 (Box 20)
        - Correspondence on Lambright v. Addison Products Co. 1979 (Box 20)
        - Social Security Cases 1978-1979 (Box 20)
        - Additional cases 1972-1979 (Box 20)
      - Case Information and Correspondence in Response to Senator Edward M. Kennedy 1979 (Box 20)
    - Opinions
      - Civil Cases
        - 1971-1972 (Box 20)
        - 1973-1975 (Box 20)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 20)
      - Criminal Cases
        - Chicago Criminal Cases 1971-1977 (Box 21)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 21)
        - 1978 (Box 21)
        - 1979 (Box 21)
      - Only in Body of Opinion "A" 1974, 1976-1978 (Box 21)
      - Race cases "B" 1973-1978 (Box 21)
      - Police cases "C" 1970-1978 (Box 21)
      - Prison cases "D" 1971-1979 (Box 21)
  - Administrative files
    The subseries includes materials related to court meetings and other administrative papers, such as case terminations and judges' memorial resolutions.
    - Service of Judge Kennedy to District Court 1981-1984 (Box 21)
    - Designations to Serve in District Court 1988-2008 (Box 21)
    - Court meetings
      - 1983 (Box 21)
      - 1984, 3 folders (Box 21)
      - 1985, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - 1987, 3 folders (Box 21)
      - 1988 (Box 21)
      - 1989, 3 folders (Box 21)
      - 1990, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - 1991, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - 1992 (Box 21)
      - 1994-1996, 3 folders (Box 21)
      - 1997, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - 1998, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - 2001 (Box 22)
    - Bankruptcy Court--Judge Vacancy 1989-1992 (Box 22)
    - Federal Public Defender
      - Bowden v. Kennedy et al 1995-1996 (Box 22)
      - Metcalf v. Martin et al 1997 (Box 22)
      - Metcalf v. Kennedy et al 1999-2001 (Box 22)
      - United States v. Hatter 2001-2002 (Box 22)
    - Case terminations 1999-2012, 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Memorial Resolutions
      - Smith, Talbot and Lawrence Gubow 1978-1984, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Thornton, Thomas P. 1985-1987 (Box 22)
      - Freeman, Ralph M. 1990-1991 (Box 22)
      - Brown, Bailey 2005 (Box 22)
      - Neilson, Susan Bieke 2006 (Box 22)
    - Administrative Office of the U.S. Courts, Electronic Case Files Project 1996-1997 (Box 22)
  - Judicial Conferences
    The subseries contains correspondence and memoranda related to the Michigan Justice Conference, Senate Judiciary Subcommittee Report and Judicial Conference Committee Surveys, the Sixth Circuit Judicial Conferences, and the Appellate Practice Institute.
    - Michigan Justice Conference, A Public Forum on the Justice System 1995 (Box 22)
    - Senate Judiciary Subcommittee Report and Judicial Conference Committee Survey 1999, 2005 (Box 22)
    - Sixth Circuit Judicial Conferences
      - 1981, 1983, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - 1984-1986, 3 folders (Box 22)
      - 1987 (Box 22)
      - 1988-1993, 6 folders (Box 22)
      - 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - 2001 (Box 22)
    - Appellate Practice Institute
      - 1983 (Box 22)
      - 1990 (Box 22)
      - 1995 (Box 22)
  - Circuit Court Committee Files